<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <atom:link href="http://example.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <link>http://example.com/</link>
    <description></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 19:59:05 -0500</pubDate>
    
      <item>
        <title>TECDP Intern Project 2016</title>
        <link>http://example.com/2016/08/19/TECDP-intern-project-2.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://example.com/2016/08/19/TECDP-intern-project-2.html</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;For the summer of 2016, I took a role as a project manager with Cigna’s Technology Early Career Development Program, and as part of that, I worked as an application developer for a mobile web application with a virtual reality component targeting millennials with mental health issues. I worked on a team of eight interns in a subteam of four developers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This application leveraged several technologies:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Twitter Bootstrap&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Angular Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A-Frame HTML (Virtual Reality Framework)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I effectively presented this application to a panel made up of leaders in the company’s IT department, including the company’s Vice President of Information Technology.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Raúl Zurita</title>
        <link>http://example.com/2016/05/10/Ra-l-Zurita.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://example.com/2016/05/10/Ra-l-Zurita.html</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;During my time as a student at the Complutense University of Madrid, I developed a responsive web application for a project taken on for a class - Hispanoamerican Literature - with collaborative partner Meredith Goodall. This project was an analisis of Raúl Zurita’s life as an author and of some of his works. Meredith created all content, and I created all HTML and CSS files.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This application leveraged Twitter Bootstrap.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The entire project can be found &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/ndleisur/Ra-l-Zurita&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; on my github.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>El ABÑ del Joven Filólogo</title>
        <link>http://example.com/2016/02/08/el-abn.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://example.com/2016/02/08/el-abn.html</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;When I was studying at the Complutense University of Madrid, I took a course called Informatics Tools Oriented for the Instruction of the Spanish Language. As a part of this course, I managed technical support for a team of four linguistics students. In this role I taught my team the fundamentals of web development and managed a website to display the project’s contents. I was also the lead for all technical support members in the class. As a part of this, I gave several lectures on basic HTML and CSS and assisted with the creation and maintenance of seven other project websites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The entirety of communication done in these roles was in Spanish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My team’s project details four different technologies useful to those who do research in the field of linguistics, including online dictionaries and corpora. You can find the finished project site &lt;a href=&quot;http://elabn.weebly.com/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>TECDP Intern Project 2015</title>
        <link>http://example.com/2015/08/14/TECDP-intern-project-1.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://example.com/2015/08/14/TECDP-intern-project-1.html</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;For the summer of 2015, I took a role as an application developer with Cigna’s Technology Early Career Development Program, and as part of that, I worked as an application developer for a mobile web application targeting caregivers. I worked on a team of thirty interns in a subteam of seven.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This application leveraged several technologies:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Twitter Bootstrap&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Angular Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;HTML5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My team presented this application to a panel made up of leaders in the company’s IT department, including the company’s Global Chief Information Officer, and was awarded first place among all teams to present.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
